Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files 1919-2015 MS 3009-RG 13
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - New York City
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: L, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 26)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Labor, Department of, 1955-1966, 1981 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 27)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Labor Relations, Office of, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 28)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Landmark Preservation Commission, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 1991, Folder 29-31)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Landmark Preservation Commission, 1961-1980 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 1-2)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Law, Department of, 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 8)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Legislative Office of Budget Review, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 9)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Licenses, Department of, 1955-1966 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Maa-Mz, 1957-1992, undated (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 11-20)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Management and Budget, Office of, 1961-1983 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 21-23)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Manhattan Borough Board, 1977 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 24)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Manpower and Career Development Agency, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 25)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Marine and Aviation, Department of, 1952-1980, 1990 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 26)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Markets, Department of, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 27)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Office Commissions, Councils, Panels, 1967-1978 (Offsite-box 1938, Folder 28-30)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mayor's Office Commissions, Councils, Panels, 1959-1986 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 1-14)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Midtown Planning and Development, Office of, 1978-1980 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 15)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Mollen Commission, 1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 16)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Municipal Services Administration, 1977 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 17)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: N, 1952, 1966, 1982-1983, 1992 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 18)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Neighborhood City Halls Program, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 19)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Neighborhood Government, Office of, 1972 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 20)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Neighborhood Services, Office of, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 21)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: O, 1975-1988 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 22)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Off-Track Betting Corporation, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 23-26)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Organization, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 27-29)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: P, 1939, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 30)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parking Violations Bureau, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 31-34)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parks, Department of, 1963-1970, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1939, Folder 35-41)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Parks-Planning, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 1-17)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Ports-Probation, 1956, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 18-21)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Proposed, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 22-25)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Proposed, 1966 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 3)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Public Events-Real Estate, 1959-1991 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 26-32)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Real Estate, Bureau of, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Real Estate-Rent and Housing Maintenance, 1959-1983 (Offsite-box 1940, Folder 33-36)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Rent and Rehabilitation Administration, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Rent Guidelines Board, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 2)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Sa-Sz, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 3-7)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Sanitation-Temporary Commission on City Finances, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 1992, Folder 5-39)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Temporary Commission on Education, 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 1993, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Traffic, 1956-1990 (Offsite-box 1993, Folder 2-5)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transit Authority, 1961-1966, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 1993, Folder 6-26)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Transit Authority-U, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 1-16)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: United Nations, 1963-1991 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 17-18)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: University Relations-Water Resources, 1968-1991 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 19-23)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Water Supply, Gas and Electricity, 1954-1989 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 24-28)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Weights and Measures-Welfare, 1954-1977 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 29-33)
    - New York City: Government: Departments and Agencies: Y-Youth, 1952-1992 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 8-13)
    - New York City: Government: Deputy Mayor, 1949-1992 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 14-17)
    - New York City: Government: District Attorney, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 18-20)
    - New York City: Government: Equipment, 1983, 1989 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 21)
    - New York City: Government: Investigations, 1932, 1959-1961, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 22-24)
    - New York City: Government: Mayor, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1941, Folder 25-32)
    - New York City: Government: Mayor, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 1-4)
    - New York City: History, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 5-19)
    - New York City: History: Associations, 1970-1989 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 20)
    - New York City: History: Associations: Brooklyn Historical Society, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 21)
    - New York City: History: Associations: New-York Historical Society, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 1942, Folder 22)
    - New York City: History: Associations: New-York Historical Society, 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 1-2)
    - New York City: History: Diamond Jubilee, 1973 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 3)
    - New York City: History: Golden Jubilee, 1948-1949 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Islands, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 5-23)
    - New York City: Laws, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 24)
    - New York City: Manhattan, 1940-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 25-27)
    - New York City: Memorials and Monuments, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 28-32)
    - New York City: Metropolitan Area, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 1994, Folder 34)
    - New York City: Metropolitan Area, 1956-1987 (Offsite-box 1995, Folder 1-10)
    - New York City: Metropolitan Area: Transit, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1995, Folder 11-20)
    - New York City: Metropolitan Area: Transit, 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 1-3)
    - New York City: Metropolitan Area: Tri-State Regional Planning Commission, 1971-1982 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Name, 1959, 1976-1988 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 5)
    - New York City: Natural Resources, 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 6)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods, 1949-1993 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 7-17)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: A-B, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 18-19)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Battery, 1957-1988 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 20)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Battery Park City, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1996, Folder 21-23)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Battery Park City, 1968-1979 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 1-2)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bay Ridge, 1973-1987 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 3)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bayside, 1959, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 5-11)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bellevue South, 1965 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 12)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bensonhurst, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 13)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Borough Park, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 14)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bowery, 1942-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 15-17)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Broadway, 1939-1984, undated (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 18)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Brooklyn Heights, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 19)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Brownsville, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 20)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Bushwick, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 21)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: C, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 1997, Folder 22-23)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Canarsie, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Chelsea, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 2)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Chinatown, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 3-8)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Civic Center Manhattan, 1960-1966, 1989 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 9)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Clinton, 1952-1959, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Cobble Hill, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 11)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Columbus Circle, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 12)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Coney Island, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 13)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Cooper Square, 1956-1991 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 14)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Corona, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 15)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Crown Heights, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1998, Folder 16-18)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Crown Heights, 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: D, 1971-1992 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 2)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Downtown and Lower Manhattan, 1955-1991 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 3-8)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: E, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 9)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: East New York, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: East Side, 1932-1993 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 11-15)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: East Village, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 16-18)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: F, 1971-1991 (Offsite-box 1999, Folder 19)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Flatbush, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Flushing, 1946-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 2)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Foley Square, 1965-1985 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 3)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Forest Hills, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Forest Hills Gardens, 1976-1989 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 5)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Fort Greene, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 6)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: G, 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 7)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Garment District, 1949, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 8)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Gramercy Park, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 9)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Grand Central, 1957-1991 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Grand Concourse, 1967-1988 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 11)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Greenpoint, 1949, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 12)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Greenwich Village, 1931-1967, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 13-23)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: H, 1951, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 24)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Hammarskjold Plaza, 1961, 1971-1977 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 25)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Harlem, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2000, Folder 26-28)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Harlem, 1946-1989 (Offsite-box 2026, Folder 1-26)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Hell's Hundred Acre's, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 2026, Folder 27)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Herald Square, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2026, Folder 28)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Highbridge, 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 2026, Folder 29)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Howard Beach, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 2026, Folder 30-31)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Hub, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Hunts, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 2)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: I, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 3)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Inwood, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: J-L, 1949-1993 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 5-7)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Laurelton, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 8)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Lincoln Square, 1956-1961, 1984-1990 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 9-13)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Linear City, 1967 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 14)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Little Italy, 1972-1990 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 15)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Long Island City, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 16)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Lower East Side, 1930-1939, 1950-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 17-22)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: M, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 23-24)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Manhattan Landing, 1972, 1984 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 25)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Midtown, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2027, Folder 26)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Midtown, 1972-1986 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 1-2)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Morningside Heights, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 3-5)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Morrisania, 1953-1956, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 6)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Mott Haven, 1968, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 7)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Murray Hill, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 8)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: N, 1962-1991 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 9)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: NoHo, 1978-1991 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: O-R, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 11-14)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Red Hook, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 15)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Rego Park, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 16)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Ridgewood, 1959, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 17)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Riverdale, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 18)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Rockaways, 1956-1991 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 19)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Rockefeller Center, 1984-1999 (Offsite-box 2028, Folder 20-25)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Rockefeller Center, 1931-1983 (Offsite-box 2029, Folder 1-14)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Rosedale, 1975-1990 (Offsite-box 2029, Folder 15)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Sa-Sz, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 2029, Folder 16-18)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Sheepshead Bay, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 2029, Folder 19-20)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: SoHo, 1970-1993 (Offsite-box 2029, Folder 21-25)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: South Bronx, 1993 (Offsite-box 2029, Folder 26)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: South Bronx, 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 1-12)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: South Street Seaport, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 13-15)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Southeast Bronx, 1972 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 16)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Sunset Park, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 17)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Sutton Place, 1962-1990 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 18)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: T, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 19)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Television City, 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 20)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Times Square, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2030, Folder 21-24)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Times Square, 1941-1989 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 1-16)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Tompkins Square, 1964, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 17)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Tribeca, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 18)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: U-V, 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 19-20)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: W, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 1943, Folder 33)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Wall Street, 1959-1993 (Offsite-box 1944, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Washington Heights, 1963-1993 (Offsite-box 1944, Folder 2-5)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Washington Square, 1950-1989 (Offsite-box 1944, Folder 6-7)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Waterfront, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 1944, Folder 8)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: West Side, 1949-1993 (Offsite-box 1944, Folder 9-27)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Williamsburg, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 1945, Folder 1)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: World Financial Center, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 1945, Folder 2-3)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: X-Y, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 1945, Folder 4-5)
    - New York City: Neighborhoods: Yorkville, 1939, 1950-1990 (Offsite-box 1945, Folder 6)
    - New York City: Parks, 1948-1993 (Offsite-box 1945, Folder 7-24)
    - New York City: Parks: A-B, 1975-1992 (Offsite-box 1945, Folder 25)
    - New York City: Parks: C-Z, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1946, Folder 1-9)
    - New York City: Parks: Battery Park, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 1946, Folder 10)
    - New York City: Parks: Breezy Point Park, 1962-1967, 1982 (Offsite-box 1946, Folder 11)
    - New York City: Parks: Bryant Park, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 1946, Folder 12)
    - New York City: Parks: Central Park, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 1946, Folder 13-22)
    - New York City: Parks: Central Park, 1944-1968, 1977-1982 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 1-15)
    - New York City: Parks: Christopher Park, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 16)
    - New York City: Parks: Crotona Park, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 17)
    - New York City: Parks: Damrosch Park, 1966-1988 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 18)
    - New York City: Parks: Flushing Meadows, 1949-1992 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 19)
    - New York City: Parks: Flushing Meadows: Corona Park, 1967-1993 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 20)
    - New York City: Parks: Fort Tyron Park, 1976-1992 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 21)
    - New York City: Parks: Gramercy Park, 1956-1991 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 21)
    - New York City: Parks: Madison Square, 1965-1992 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 22)
    - New York City: Parks: Morningside Park, 1961-1990 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 23)
    - New York City: Parks: Prospect Park, 1959, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 24-25)
    - New York City: Parks: Riverside Park, 1963-1993 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 26)
    - New York City: Parks: Tompkins Square Park, 1967, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1947, Folder 27-28)
    - New York City: Parks: Union Square Park, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 22)
    - New York City: Parks: Van Cortland Park, 1961-1993 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 23)
    - New York City: Parks: Washington Square Park, 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 24)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1993 (Offsite-box 2031, Folder 25)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2032, Folder 1-15)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 2033, Folder 1-16)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 2034, Folder 1-14)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1983-1987 (Offsite-box 2035, Folder 1-14)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 2036, Folder 1-13)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1969-1977 (Offsite-box 2037, Folder 1-16)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 2038, Folder 1-19)
    - New York City: Politics: General, 1931-1965 (Offsite-box 2039, Folder 1-17)
    - New York City: Politics: Election System, 1951-1993 (Offsite-box 2040, Folder 1-3)
    - New York City: Politics: History, 1931-1993 (Offsite-box 2040, Folder 4)
    - New York City: Politics: Official Election Statistics, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 2040, Folder 5)
    - New York City: Politics: Parties, 1941-1993 (Offsite-box 2040, Folder 6-34)
    - New York City: Polls, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2040, Folder 35)
    - New York City: Population, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2040, Folder 36-43)
    - New York City: Population, 1930-1985 (Offsite-box 2041, Folder 1-26)
    - New York City: Port, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 2041, Folder 27-34)
    - New York City: Port, 1932-1980 (Offsite-box 2042, Folder 1-21)
    - New York City: Port: Citizen Waterfront Committee, 1956, 1979 (Offsite-box 2042, Folder 22)
    - New York City: Port: Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2042, Folder 23-34)
    - New York City: Port: Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, 1932-1981 (Offsite-box 2043, Folder 1-21)
    - New York City: Port: Waterfront Commission, 1953-1989 (Offsite-box 2043, Folder 22-26)
    - New York City: Publications, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 2043, Folder 27)
    - New York City: Public Works, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 2043, Folder 28)
    - New York City: Public Works, 1956-1989, undated (Offsite-box 2044, Folder 1-4)
    - New York City: Queens, 1937-1938, 1952-1993 (Offsite-box 2044, Folder 5-10)
    - New York City: State Relations, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2044, Folder 11-19)
    - New York City: State Relations, 1937, 1959-1975 (Offsite-box 2045, Folder 1-2)
    - New York City: Staten Island, 1930-1993, undated (Offsite-box 2045, Folder 3-9)
    - New York City: Streets: General, 1947-1993 (Offsite-box 2045, Folder 10-17)
    - New York City: Streets: A; Atlantic Avenue; Avenue of the Americas, 1967, 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 2045, Folder 18-20)
    - New York City: Streets: Avenue of the Americas, 1941-1969 (Offsite-box 2046, Folder 1-2)
    - New York City: Streets: B; Bleecker Street; Bowery; Borad Street; Broadway; Broome Street, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 2046, Folder 3-9)
    - New York City: Streets: Ca-Cz; Charlotte Street; Columbus Avenue, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 2046, Folder 10-14)
    - New York City: Streets: D-E; Eighty-Fifth Street; Eighty-Fourth Street, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 2046, Folder 15-18)
    - New York City: Streets: Fa-Fz; Fifth Avenue; Forty-Second Street; Fourteenth Street, 1937-1993 (Offsite-box 2046, Folder 19-22)
    - New York City: Streets: G-M; MacDougal Street; Madison Avenue, 1942-1993 (Offsite-box 2073, Folder 2-9)